<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Justin DeBo</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Justin DeBo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2020 07:53:07 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Music</title>
      <link>/about/music/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2020 07:53:07 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/music/</guid>
      <description>Music has been a big part of my life since I picked up my first pair of drumsticks in fourth grade. In high school at Normal Community West I was introduced to marching band, and to this day I continue my work with that same program as an instructor for their drumline. In college my musical studies continued, taking me to Cuba with the Millikin percussion studio to study Afro-Cuban music, to Australia with my former high school to perform at the Sidney Opera House, and back to Cuba to perform with the Millikin Latin Jazz Project at the Havana International Jazz Festival.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bio</title>
      <link>/about/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2019 07:53:07 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/bio/</guid>
      <description>A little bit about me&amp;hellip;
I&amp;rsquo;m an experienced software developer with a love of music. Many years ago I began studying music as a possible career path. Through that pursuit I learned the value of criticism, developed a sense of creativity and got comfortable performing under pressure. Now I try to apply those same skills in the business world - whether it&amp;rsquo;s setting my ego aside during code reviews, solving architecture challenges or making technical topics digestible in executive briefings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cuba</title>
      <link>/posts/music/cuba/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2019 07:53:07 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/music/cuba/</guid>
      <description>In 2015 I got my first opportunity to visit Havana Cuba with the Millikin Percussion Studio. While we were there we spent a week studying Cuban folkloric and popular music with some of the most renowned teachers in the country. After returning from that trip and joining Millikin&amp;rsquo;s Latin Jazz project, I got to record an album inspired by the Afro-Cuban rhythms and songs we learned while we were there. Balance Issues combined elements of rhumba, salsa and comparsa music with jazz and funk to make a series of songs that are both fun to dance to and exciting to perform!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/</guid>
      <description>Justin DeBo 1901 Claremont Commons Normal, Illinois 61761 | (309) 533 – 9050 | justin.debo@gmail.com
Education Millikin University Decatur, Illinois
Bachelor of Science in Information Systems, May 2018
Concentration: Data Management
Minor in Music
Work Experience  State Farm Insurance Bloomington, IL Summer 2017 – Present  Big Data Developer - Test Data Privacy  Supported sensitive data scanning Hadoop application that ingests data from all enterprise test systems. Supported Splunk application that monitors inbound/outbound traffic to test DB2 Systems Worked on committee focused on accelerating AWS adoption across Enterprise Data Systems area  Data Analyst - Total Loss Technology  Provided ad hoc DB2 reports for Total Loss Claims business partners to respond to production outages.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>